#### Contact

maredyth28@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/maredyth-walters-98bb8722 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Healthcare Nursing Clinical Research

Certifications
Certified Critical Care Nurse
Certified Case Manager

# Maredyth Walters

RN, MSN, CCRN, CCM Macon, Georgia Area

#### Summary

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, Critical Care, Care Coordination, Strategic Planning, and Medicine. Strong operations professional with a Master of Science (M.S.) focused in Nursing Education from South University.

### Experience

Navicent Health
Nurse Director, Renal Care Services
2013 - Present (7 years)
Company changed name- employee since 1988

Medical Center of Central Georgia
Director - Care Coordination and Logistics
March 2012 - May 2013 (1 year 3 months)
Macon, Georgia Area

Macon State College Adjunct Faculty September 2009 - May 2012 (2 years 9 months) Macon, Georgia Area

Clinical instructor

Medical Center of Central Georgia Assistant Nurse Director - Neuro Services May 2011 - March 2012 (11 months)

Medical Center of Central Georgia Clinical educator 2008 - 2011 (3 years)

## Education

South University

Master of Science (M.S.), Nursing Education  $\cdot$  (2010)

Middle Georgia State University

 $\label{eq:Bachelor} \textbf{Bachelor of Science (B.S.)}, \ \textbf{Registered Nursing}, \ \textbf{Nursing Administration},$ 

Nursing Research and Clinical Nursing